I made a little world one afternoon
Just squares and skies of painted blue
A bird that never asked to fly
Until somebody pressed “Retry”
I thought a score would make it last
A number no one could surpass
But numbers only learned to grow
While all the names were left below
If every update hides a trace
Would someone still remember this place?
If every version fades away
Will anybody choose to stay?
Don’t chase the highest score tonight
Follow where the echoes hide
Some stories never reach “The End”
Until somebody plays again
If one more heart can hear this song
Then maybe nothing’s truly gone
The sky was never made to keep
Only those who dared to leap
The world moved on to brighter screens
To faster dreams and newer things
But somewhere underneath the code
The little road still waits alone
The final notes were always there
Just no one stayed to hear them end
You found the path
They couldn’t see
The missing line
Inside of me
No cheats
No myths
No perfect run
Just someone
Who finally listened
Thank you for reaching the end.